amod.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy

## How We Protect Your Privacy

National Partitions is committed to ensuring the privacy and accuracy of your personal information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from our web servers with non-affiliated companies or individuals.

## Information We Gather

Our web servers generate temporary logs that contain the following information:

  * Internet address of computer being used
  * Webpage's requested
  * Referring webpage
  * Browser used
  * Date and Time

The data is used in aggregate by system administrators and web content managers to tune the website for its efficiency and is not ordinarily associated with specific individuals. Raw data from the web server logs is only shared with the content manager of each website. Summary reports produced from the logs help Web publishers determine what Web browsers and pages are most popular.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored by the Web browser. Cookies are often used to remember information about preferences and pages you have visited. You can refuse to accept cookies, can disable cookies, and remove cookies from your hard drive. In Netscape Navigator, choose Edit and Preferences to manage your cookie settings, in Internet Explorer select Tools and Internet Options. National Partitions currently does not employ cookies.

## Security and Accuracy of Confidential Information

National Partitions does its best to ensure that the personal information we have about you is accurate. Although no computer system is 100% secure, the National Partitions website and associated computer infrastructure employs extensive security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control.

## Sharing of Information

National Partitions does not and will not willingly share your personal information with any third party with the exception of National Partitions distributors in cases where you have requested distributor information or price quotes.

## Questions

If you have questions about this privacy statement or you believe that your personal information has been released without your consent, please contact us using our contact form.
